(DOORBELL RINGING)
Is Riley here?
Red alert!
- (ALARM BLARING)
- AUTOMATED VOICE: Boy. Boy.
AUTOMATED VOICE: Boy. Boy. Boy.
There's a boy in my house.
I knew she was going skating,
but I thought it was with her friends.
Why is there a boy in my house?
This isn't a date, is it? I'll ask Riley.
I don't like this.
This can't be a date! She's only 12!
Let's probe, but layer it
with cool words the kids say,
so it's not obvious.
So, what's the dealio with Jordan?
O- M-G, he is awesome-sauce
fo sheezy.
MOM: I'm not playin'.
Did she just say "fo sheezy"?
I don't understand. What's happening?
Ugh, this is just embarrassing.
I can't. I can't.
MOM: Holla!
(SNIFFLES)
I know what you're doing here, Jordan.
You don't think that I know what
you know, but I know, you little punk!
He's not good enough for Riley.
No one is!
Go back to jail!
DAD'S ANGER: What are you
looking for, Jordan? Something to steal?
- Like our daughter.
- Should we say something?
No, no, no. He'll be expecting that.
Give him the silent treatment.
He's about to crack, I can feel it.
- (LOUD ROCK MUSIC PLAYING)
- Whoa, dude! Awesome!
Sir, no response.
Two can play at your mind games,
Jordan. Intimidate!
(INHALES SHARPLY)
Dude, what's he looking at?
Probably your dumb hat.
(CHUCKLES)
- Whoa!
- (LAUGHING)
- (GRUNTS)
- (CRASHING)
(CHUCKLES)
- Sir, intimidation is failing.
- (SCOFFS)
Increase the pressure. Engage.
So, Jordan,
what do you like to do for fun?
I don't know. Stuff.
Sir, that sounds like backtalk.
(GROANS) That's it! He's outta here!
Give him the boot.
Yes, sir. Launching boot.
(ALARM BLARING)
On my mark. In five, four, three...
Oh...
I play in a band. That's fun.
Wait. We were in a band.
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYING)
I was in a band, lead guitar.
Cool. I rock the bass.
- We played a lot ofAC/DC.
- Yeah, my favorite band is AC/DC.
- (GASPS)
- What.
Mom, ew, it's not a date.
We're going skating
with a group of friends.
Oh, fun. That'll be off the hook. L-O-L.
Stop talking like that!
Wait. Where's Jordan?
Did you leave Jordan with Dad?
Mom! This is so embarrassing.
Riley, your father
would never do any...
(LOUD ROCK MUSIC PLAYING)
Yeah!
- Awesome.
- (CRASHING)
Bye, Mom. Bye, Dad.
- Have fun.
- Peace out, my homies.
You know, Jordan's a good kid.
You're not so bad yourself.
Sir, the wife has initiated contact.
What do we do?
This is our chance. Give her the look.
(SCOFFS) He's making
that stupid face again.
MOM'S ANGER: Ugh.
Should we smack him?
Come on. He's adorable.
There's the signal.
- (KEYBOARDS CLACKING)
- We are go. Repeat, we are go.
Contact in five, four, three, two...
- (CHEERING)
- (LOUD ROCK MUSIC PLAYING)
(EXPLOSION)
(POP MUSIC PLAYING)
I'm good. You guys good?
- Yeah. I'm good.
- Yeah, I'm good here.
- Good.
- (MUSIC STOPS PLAYING)
Okay, that's enough.
Ah, yeah.
Um... I'll go fix the table.